Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.A. Hedley Donovan Files, 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979); 56.0 Linear feet; (56 boxes)
  - Subsubseries I.A.1. Subject Files, 1948-1983; 35.0 Linear feet; (35 boxes)
    - Duplicates: Reminiscence: A-Z, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 19)
    - Duplicates: Russia notes: Interview with Khrushchev, 1958 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 20)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: Misc., 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 21)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: List, 1973 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 22)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: Research and Misc., 1956-1982 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 23-24)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: Research: Dinner on the Khrushchev tapes: 1974 April 11 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 25)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: Research: Future of magazines talk: 1972 March 16 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 26)
    - Duplicates: Speeches: Research: December 8 Action, 1965 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 27)
    - Duplicates: Speeches and Memos, 1955-1963 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 28-29)
    - Duplicates: Suggestions, 1976 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 30)
    - Duplicates: Time essay: "America and the World Out There": 1975 May 19 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 31)
    - Duplicates: Time essay: "South America: Notes on a New Continent": 1975 December 1 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 32)
    - Duplicates: Time essay: "The Good Uses of the Watergate Affair": 1973 May 14 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 33)
    - Duplicates: Time essay: "Coming to Terms with Vietnam": 1971 June 14 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 34)
    - Duplicates: Time Interviews, 1973 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 35)
    - Duplicates: Time Inc. staff meeting: 1977 March 10 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 36)
    - Duplicates: Time Inc. staff meeting: 1976 March 18 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 37)
    - Duplicates: Time Inc. staff meeting: 1974 December 12 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 38)
    - Duplicates: Time Inc.: Subjects: A-Z, 1958-1980 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 39-41)
    - Duplicates: Trips: Russia, Warsaw, Copenhagen, 1958 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 42)
    - Duplicates: Vietnam: Misc. articles and reports, undated (Offsite-box 758, Folder 43)
    - Duplicates: Vietnam: Piece for Life: 1966 February 25 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 44)
    - Duplicates: White House appointment: Letters of congratulations: A-Z, 1979 (Offsite-box 758, Folder 45)
    - Duplicates: White House appointment: Misc., 1979 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 1)
    - Duplicates: White House: Cocktail party: 1980 September 22 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 2)
    - Duplicates: White House: Exit: 1980 August (Offsite-box 759, Folder 3)
    - Duplicates: White House: National agenda: 1980 February (Offsite-box 759, Folder 4)
    - Duplicates: White House: Misc., 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 5)
    - Duplicates: Worries about Woman's Mag at Time Inc., 1977 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 6)
  - Subsubseries I.A.2. Trips, 1952-1982, undated; 4.0 Linear feet; (4 boxes)
    Organized alphabetically, primarily by geographic place, with general files at the front.
    Trips contains primarily travel files with some notes and writings interspersed such as Arguments, Attitude, Khrushchev, Personal, and Why Supreme Soviet Elections. All are duplicated files, but not all of the materials are copies created by the Time Inc. Archives. The files include some original copies, extra copies, carbon copies, and a very few original items.
    - Trips, 1952-1981 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 7)
    - Lists, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 8)
    - Trip A: 1976 October, 1976, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 9)
    - Time Africa/Mid East News Tour: March 16-April 1, 1978 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 10)
    - African trip (with Heiskells): Didn't happen: December 30, 1976-January 27, 1977, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 11)
    - Alexandria, Washington D.C.: December 2-3, 1976 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 12)
    - London: Bonnie Angelo's party: January 29-February 1, 1978 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 13)
    - Anglo-American Conference: December 6-8, 1968 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 14)
    - Arden House notes, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 15)
    - Argentina, 1975 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 16)
    - Arguments, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 17)
    - Asia News Tour: January 31-February 14, 1965 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 18)
    - Atlanta with Governor Jimmy Carter: December 2-4, 1973, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 19)
    - Attitude toward America, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 20)
    - Bilderberg Meeting: Milan-London-Spain: March 31-April 19, 1965 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 21)
    - Bilderberg Meetings: Aachen, London, Rome: April 16-28, 1980 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 22)
    - Montreal-Ottawa, Canada: Time Inc. Board Meetings: November 16-18, 1966 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 23)
    - Time Inc. Board of Directors; Alexandria meeting and Washington reception: March 16-17, 1977 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 24)
    - Boston: December 8, 1971 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 25)
    - Boston: Massachusetts Investor Trust Dinner: October 14, 1964 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 26)
    - Boston Trip: November 7-9, 1969 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 27)
    - Boston University Commencement: May 19, 1968 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 28)
    - Brazil, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 29)
    - Cairo: January 1979 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 30)
    - California election coverage: September 29-October 6, 1972 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 31)
    - Cambridge Seminar Speaker Schedule: Program Details: January 1, 1974, 1973, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 32)
    - Canada: Montreal, Ottawa, Toronto: October 11-14, 1971 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 33)
    - Caneel Bay: January 8-18, 1973 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 34)
    - Caneel Bay: January 16-25, 1978: Cancelled (Offsite-box 759, Folder 35)
    - Caribbean: Grenada, Martinique by charter, then Caneel Bay: January 3-19, 1972 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 36)
    - Carter, 1976 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 37)
    - Chicago: March 1961 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 38)
    - Chicago: May 5-6, 1970 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 39)
    - Chicago Annual Meeting: April 20-21, 1966 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 40)
    - Chicago Reception: November 23, 1971 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 41)
    - Chicago trip, plus Washington: September 22-25, 1975 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 42)
    - Chile, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 43)
    - China, 1979 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 44)
    - People's Republic of China: Peking, Hong Kong: January 20-28, 1979 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 45)
    - Boston: Choate Club: Harvard Visiting Committee: March 11-12, 1968 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 46)
    - Cleveland-Chicago Trip: October 24-29, 1967 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 47)
    - Conclusions, undated (Offsite-box 759, Folder 48)
    - Confederation of British Individuals: London: December 3-5, 1971 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 49)
    - Conference on the Presidency: Minneapolis: November 5-7, 1982 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 50)
    - Congressional Seminar: Washington, D.C.: May 19, 1975 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 51)
    - Convention: Chicago, 1952 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 52)
    - Dartmouth Conference II: With Russians: December 3-7, 1972 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 53)
    - Dartmouth Conference VIII: Soviet Union: April 21-25, 1974 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 54)
    - Dartmouth Conference VII: Carnegie endowment: Time Inc. conference on anti-trust laws: Williamsburg, Washington: May 4-8, 1979 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 55)
    - Delos Symposium and Greece: July 13-26, 1966 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 56)
    - Democratic and Republican Political Conventions: Miami Beach: July 1972 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 57)
    - Detroit-Pittsburgh: June 2-3, 1964 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 58)
    - News Tour of Eastern Europe: October 20-November 2, 1966 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 59)
    - Economy (Offsite-box 759, Folder 60)
    - England, and DD to Amsterdam: May 4-18, 1976 (DD May 22) (Offsite-box 759, Folder 61)
    - England, East Germany, Sweden: June 14-28, 1970 (Offsite-box 759, Folder 62)
    - Europe: May 4-June 14, 1955 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 1)
    - Europe: June 1959 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 2)
    - Europe: Includes London board meeting: May 12-June 9, 1963 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 3)
    - European Businessmen's Tour of the United States, 1968 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 4)
    - European sales convention and Paris: Juan Les-Pins: June 16-23, 1966 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 5)
    - European Trip: February 11-24, 1968 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 6)
    - Exxon Gulf Coast Expedition: July 8-9, 1974 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 7)
    - Far East Trip: April 8-29, 1973 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 8)
    - Far East Trip: Japan, Korea, Okinawa, Hong Kong, Vietnam: October 19-November 24, 1965 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 9-10)
    - Florida primary trip: Tampa-Miami: March 8-11, 1972: Cancelled (Offsite-box 760, Folder 11)
    - Foliage watching: Williamstown-Bucks County: October 15-19, 1971 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Policy Seminar: Washington, D.C.: November 11-12, 1974 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 13)
    - France-Germany: May 21-June 11, 1977 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 14)
    - Harvard and Yale: April 7-9, 1970 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 15)
    - Hawaii, Los Angeles, San Francisco: September 20-24, 1968, 1968, undated (Offsite-box 760, Folder 16)
    - Hedley Donovan trip: June 1977 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 17)
    - Hilton Head, South Carolina: March 21-31, 1969 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 18)
    - Houston: Board meeting: September 15-17, 1970 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 19)
    - Indianapolis trip: December 1-2, 1969 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 20)
    - Indonesia: February 1967 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 21)
    - Ireland: Reading: June 6, 1972 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 22)
    - Italy: October 1961 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 23)
    - Jamaica and St. John Vacation: January 1-13 and January 18-25, 1970 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 24)
    - Japan: October 1965 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 25)
    - Johnson, President Lyndon B.: Weekend at the LBJ ranch: December 16-18, 1966 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 26)
    - Johnson, President Lyndon B.: Weekend at Ranch: December 1966, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 760, Folder 27)
    - Khrushchev, undated (Offsite-box 760, Folder 28)
    - Lake Mohonk: Carnegie Endowment Trustee's meeting: May 22-24, 1970 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 29)
    - Life Space Tour: November 29-December 5, 1964 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 30)
    - Life Space Tour: March 27-30, 1966 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 31)
    - Little Brown Reception: Daedalus Meeting: Boston: October 31-November 2, 1968 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 32)
    - London, January 9-13, 1963 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 33)
    - London, Germany, Paris: Interiors, contacts: June 1959 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 34)
    - London, India, Bangkok, Djakarta, Singapore, Australia: February 5-March 1, 1967 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 35-37)
    - London, Middle East (Cairo, Ammani, Damascus, Baghdad), Rome: December 30, 1978-January 16, 1979, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 38)
    - London, Paris, Germany trip: February 11-24, 1968 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 39)
    - London, Paris trip notes: December 1968 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 40)
    - London, Paris, Bonn, Rome, Procigano: September 22-October 14, 1974 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 41)
    - Los Angeles: November 1960 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 42)
    - Los Angeles: La Jolla: December 5-13, 1964 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 43)
    - Los Angeles Conference: September 30-October 1, 1972 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 44)
    - Media and Society seminar: Philadelphia: April 2-4, 1982 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 45)
    - Mexico: September 8-10, 1965 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 46)
    - Mexico: Cozumel-Yucatan: January 12-26, 1974: Cancelled (Offsite-box 760, Folder 47)
    - Mexico: Yucatan-Cancun-Cozumel: February 5-17, 1975 (Offsite-box 760, Folder 48)
    - Mid East Trip: March 21-28, 1980 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 1)
    - Middle East Trip: Egypt-Moscow-Rome-Israel: April 28-May 14, 1969 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 2)
    - Middle East Trip: February 28-March 17, 1974 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 3)
    - Middle East News Tour: January 17-30, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 4)
    - Minneapolis: March 1961 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 5)
    - Minneapolis: May 1962 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 6)
    - Minneapolis: March 2-7, 1965 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 7)
    - Minneapolis: May 1968 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 8)
    - Minneapolis: April 22-25, 1971 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 9)
    - Minneapolis and Chicago trip: November 18-20, 1969: November 19 Board Meeting (Offsite-box 761, Folder 10)
    - Minneapolis-Chicago: August 16-19, 1970 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 11)
    - Minneapolis-Chicago: January 10-12, 1971 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 12)
    - Minneapolis-Chicago: University of Minneapolis Foundation: October 26-29, 1973 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 13)
    - M.I.T.: A: March 1977 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 14)
    - M.I.T.: With Louis Banks: Cambridge: April 14-16, 1977 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 15)
    - Moline, IL-Columbia, MO: April 23-26, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 16)
    - NATO Trip: Rome, Brussels, Bonn, Nuremberg, Stuttgart: June 17-27, 1981 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 17)
    - New England weekend: October 18-20, 1973 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 18)
    - North Carolina Time Inc. Seminar: November 11-13, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 19)
    - O.I.U.H.C. Reunion: Montreal: September 17-19, 1976 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 20)
    - Offutt Air Base Sac: April 23-24, 1964 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 21)
    - Okinawa: October 23, 1965 (Offsite-box 765, Folder 22)
    - Overseas trips, Summary of, undated (Offsite-box 761, Folder 23)
    - Panama, 1975, undated (Offsite-box 761, Folder 24)
    - Paris: October 1960 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 25)
    - Paris-Amsterdam: European Bureau Meeting, Paris: Europe-America Conference, Amsterdam: March 23-18, 1973 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 26)
    - Paris, India, Rome, London: Ford Foundation Meeting, India: September 17-October 19, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 27)
    - Pearl Harbor-Korea-Hong Kong, China: October-November 1965 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 28)
    - Pebble Beach, CA: Sports Illustrated sales meeting: September 17-19, 1973 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 29)
    - Peru, undated (Offsite-box 761, Folder 30)
    - Phoenix, AZ: April 1962 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 31)
    - Political swing: Kansas City-Des Moines-Urbana-Springfield-Milwaukee: September 12-20, 1972 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 32)
    - Post-trip correspondence and items: India-Australia-Far East trip: February 5-March 1, 1967 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 33)
    - Qantas. round-the-world: December 1957-January 1958, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 34)
    - Republican Convention, Kansas City: August 15-20, 197 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 35)
    - Rome-Moscow: October 17-November 2, 1980 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 36)
    - Rome-Naples: May 19-June 4, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 37)
    - Russia notes: Interviews about the U.S.S.R. in general, 1958, undated (Offsite-box 761, Folder 38)
    - Russian News Tours: Never happened, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 39)
    - Russian notes, 1968 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 40)
    - Russian trip: January 13-24, 1968 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 41)
    - Russian trip: Research and notes: April 19-May 5, 1974 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 42)
    - Russia-Siberia: Dartmouth VIII conference with Russians: April 19-May 4, 1974 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 43)
    - St. John Vacation: January 22-February 2, 1971 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 44)
    - St. Louis: September 1960 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 45)
    - St. Louis-Detroit-Chicago: October 19-20, 1964 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 46)
    - Saint Maarten: December 23-30, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 47)
    - "Security", undated (Offsite-box 761, Folder 48)
    - September-October 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 49)
    - South Africa-Kenya-Frankfurt: Ford Foundation Board Meeting: September 16-October 10, 1982 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 50)
    - South American trip: October 16-November 2, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 51)
    - South American trip and Time essay: Background material and research: October 7-November 7, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 52)
    - Sterling Forest-Washington-Nassau: December 7-13, 1970 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 53)
    - Stonehenge: The Role of Technology in the Growth of Time Inc.: October 7-8, 1968 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 54)
    - Super Bowl, New Orleans: January 10-13, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 55)
    - Super Bowl, New Orleans: January 13-16, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 56)
    - Time Asia News Tour: February 20-March 9, 1969 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 57)
    - Time (Envelope): Hotel Saint-Georges: Beirut, Lebanon, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 58)
    - Time Inc. conference on taxation: September 12-14, 1978 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 59)
    - Time News Tour Participants, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 60)
    - Time: Reports on America: October 3-8, 1971 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 61)
    - Traverse City-Los Angeles: June 7-11, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 62)
    - Turkey-Ireland: May 25-June 11, 1972 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 63)
    - Venezuela, 1975 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 64)
    - Vermont Weekend: October 1-4, 1976 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 65)
    - Vietnam notes: October 1965 (Offsite-box 761, Folder 66)
    - Vietnam trip: April 21-May 4, 1967 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 1)
    - Washington: April 18-21, 1970 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 2)
    - Washington: Gridiron Dinner: March 12-14, 1971, 1971, undated (Offsite-box 762, Folder 3)
    - Washington: July 1981 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 4)
    - Washington, D.C.: June 27-28, 1968 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 5)
    - Washington, D.C.: July 14-16, 1975 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 6)
    - Washington, D.C.: January 11-13, 1976 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 7)
    - Washington and fall leaf trip: October 3-7, 1975 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 8)
    - Washington trips, 1953 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 9)
    - Why Supreme Soviet, Elections, undated (Offsite-box 762, Folder 10)
  - Subsubseries I.A.3. Audiovisual, 1966-1977, undated; 2.0 Linear feet; (2 boxes)
    Audiovisual contains audiotape reels and audio cassettes of primarily speeches by or events attended by Hedley Donovan.
    Organized chronologically with undated material at the end.
    Access Restrictions
    Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
    - 1966 November 3 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 1)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Copy. University Foundation. Side 1 11/3/66."
    - 1966 December 20 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips. On container label: "Donovan Luncheon 12/20/66."
    - 1967 January 11 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 3)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips. On front container label: "Talk - Hedley Donovan. Jan 11, '67. Congregational Church of Manhasset." On back container label: "Track 1 only."
    - 1968 January 26 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 4)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Donovan 1/26/68."
    - 1969 February 18 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 5)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips. On label: "Occasion: Centennial Banquet. Place: Sheraton-Cleveland Hotel. Introductions: Herbert E. Strawbridge, Thomas Vail. Introducing Hedley Donovan Editor-in-Chief Time Inc. Recorder: E. Jones. C.P.L."
    - 1969 December 1 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 6)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; monaural; halftrack; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Hedley Donovan Speech-Indianapolis 12/1/69."
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; monaural; halftrack; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Hedley Donovan question and answer period following speech in Indianapolis 12/1/69."
    - 1970 March (Offsite-box 784, Folder 7)
      1 audiotape reel: analog. On container label: "Detroit speech March '70 and question and answers with Council on Foreign Relations."
      1 audiotape reel: analog.
    - 1970 March 17 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 8)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Editors and Managers for the Early '70's. Speech delivered by Hedley Donovan, Editor-in-Chief - Time, Inc. to Distinguished Visitors Series Society for Advancement of Management, Twin City Chapter. March 17, 1970."
    - 1970 November 17 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 9)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4ips; 4in. On container label: "Hedley Donovan Wildlife Congress Speech, Nov 17."
    - 1971 October 7 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 10)
      1 audiotape reel: analog. On container label: "10/7/71 This is an empty tape. Rhodes Scholar Dinner dud."
    - 1971 October 8 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 11)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "10-8-71 Couples Club. Congregational Church of Manhasset."
    - 1972 February 5 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 12)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Eagle Scout Lunch. Feb 5, 1972. Minneapolis."
    - 1972 October 13 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 13)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, On container label: "October 13, 1972. Minikahda Club. Minneapolis"
    - 1974 January 3 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 14)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: Illegible handwriting and "Talk to former Life edit staffer. 8th flr. auditorium. 1/3/74."
    - 1974 December 12 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 15)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Hedley Donovan. Time Inc. staff mtg. December 12, 1974. 8th flr auditorium."
    - 1975 April 23 (Offsite-box 784, Folder 16)
      1 audiotape reel: analog. On container label: "H. Donovan speech - Deere & Co. 'America and the World Out There.' April 23, 1975."
    - 1975 June 19 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 1)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Hedley Donovan. Time Inc. staff talk. June 19, 1975."
    - 1976 March 18 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Hedley Donovan talk to staff meeting in auditorium. 3/18/76 4:30 pm."
    - 1976 March 23 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 3)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "World Affairs Council -- Boston, March 23, 1976."
    - 1976 June 2 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 4)
      1 audiocassette (Sony DC-90): analog. On label: "June 2, 1976. Hedley Donovan talk to Chicago Council on Foreign Rel."
    - 1976 October 6 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 5)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips. On container label: "Reel 1. Bohemian Club Art Gallery. 10-6-76. 7 1/2 ips / 1/2 track. Recorded on both sides. HD Speech -- San Francisco. Business and the Press."
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips. On container label: "Reel 2. Bohemian Club Art Gallery. 10-6-76. 7 1/2 ips / 1/2 track. Recorded on one side only."
    - 1977 April 27 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 6)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: " Money staff meeting. April 27, 1977."
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 1/4 in. tape. On container label: " Money staff meeting. (second tape). April 27, 1977."
    - 1977 May 19 (Offsite-box 785, Folder 7)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Speed 3 3/4. Date 5/19/77. Subject: Fortune's. Place: 47th Floor T&L Bldg. Speakers. H. Donovan 0000 to 0380 on 3 3/4. Lubar 0381."
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 8)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Tuesday May 21. Hedley Donovan. Fortune Ponte Vedra. Convention Speech."
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 9)
      1 audiotape reel: analog. On container label: "Hedley Donovan's Speech at A.I.M.E. Banquet."
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 10)
      1 audiocassette (recoton 90): analog in., 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Labeled side 1 and side 2.